recurrent network의 파라메터
업데이트를 계산하기 위해서는
To compute the parameter
updates of a recurrent network,
시간의 미분값을 backpropagate
할 필요가 있습니다.
we need to backpropagate
the derivative through time,
sequence의 시작부분에서의 모든 방법은
all the way to the beginning
of the sequence.
실제적으로는 더 자주, 우리가
감당할 수 있을만큼의 많은 단계에서
Or in practice, more often, for
as many steps as we can afford.
모든 미분값들은 같은 파라메터를
적용합니다.
All these derivatives are going to
be applied to the same parameters.
한번에 업데이트되는 연관된 모든 값들은
같은 가중치를 갖습니다.
That's a lot of correlated updates
all at once, for the same weights.
Stochastic gradient descent에서는
나쁜 결과가 나옵니다.
This is bad for
stochastic gradient descent.
Stochastic gradient descent은
parameters에 대해서 연관되지 않은 업데이트로 간주합니다.
Stochastic gradient descent
prefers to have uncorrelated updates,
training의 안정성을 위해서..
to its parameters, for
the stability of the training.
이것은 매우 수리적으로 매우 불안정합니다.
This makes the math very unstable.
기울기가 지수적으로 증가해서
무한으로 발산하거나
Either the gradients grow exponentially
and you end up with infinities.
기울기가 떨어져서 매우 빨리 zero로 수렴합니다.
Or they go down to zero very quickly.
어느쪽도 training을 끝나지 못합니다.
And you end up not training anything.